What is this already?
I am inspired to try all kinds of things!
There you go.
Hello everyone!
I'm attendance number 11, Kobayashi Hanatootsu, from Shirito-Yuyubi Shugaku.
I'd like to try my hand at DIY again this time.
I'm going to try my best to show beginners that it's fun.
I'll do my best to make it fun for beginners.
Please subscribe to my channel and give me a high rating!
Please subscribe to my channel and give me a high rating.
What do you want to try this time?
Wood table
Wood Table
Creamer.
I'm worried about you.
I'm a little worried.
I'm a little worried about you, but I'm going to make a new outfit for you today.
Yes, of course.
I don't know if it'll work.
Log Log DIY
Bunkei-san I'm going to make a wood table.
Bunkei-san But if you cut the wood a little...
Bunkei-san There are a lot of wood chips in there.
Bunkei-san I asked him to wear a mask and goggles
Akarin I thought it looks like that too.
Akarin I'm a little excited
Bunkei-san, you are a beginner, aren't you?
Akarin Yes, that's right.
Bunkei As expected of a beginner, making a table is a bit difficult.
Akarin That's right, it's a bit difficult.
Bunkei, I'll call a carpenter.
Mr. Bunkei, I'm Mr. Kobayashi, a carpenter.
Kobayashi-san, nice to meet you.
Kobayashi-san. Pleased to meet you.
Bunkei-san, if there's anything you don't understand today...
Bunkei-san Basically, let's have the carpenter help us.
Bunkei-san First, let's cut the wood for the table's foundation.
Kobayashi Yes, the wood for the base.
Bunkei-san, measure the length for now.
Kobayashi, yes.
Bunkei-san, let's cut it down.
Kobayashi By the way, what is this already?
Bunkei-san This is a tabletop electric round
Kobayashi, this is an electric circle.
Kobayashi You must be a professional carpenter.
Kobayashi I have this image that only a professional carpenter can handle it.
Bunkei If you're careful
Bunkei Everyone can use it.
Kobayashi Yes.
Bunkei-san Lumber for now.
Bunkei Then, legs and...
Bunkei-san, we'll make a base and a table like this.
Bunkei, I'll make a table.
Bunkei-san, I'll demonstrate.
Kobayashi, that's hard to see.
Bunkei-san, hold the wood with this so it doesn't move.
Kobayashi Oh.
I'll show you in a very simple way.
It's like this.
It's like sashimi.
Like a whole tuna
I'll measure the length.
Like this.
This is a measuring scale.
I'm going to make a table 400 meters high today.
Okay.
Mark it.
That's a stabbing iron.
Now, we're going to match them up.
I'll get you to ink it.
Ah...
Here.
Set it up.
First, look at it from the side like this.
This circle is where the blade meets the line.
Here you go.
Align it.
So that it doesn't move.
This will hold the wood in place.
Now stand in front of me.
Yes, sir.
Put your left hand over here.
Hold it down.
May I?
Yes, ma'am.
Yes, please.
I'm nervous.
Oh!
You're good!
Oh! Amazing!
You're the sharpest...
Wow! That's amazing! I've never done that before!
Dennoko? A hacksaw?
Electric circular saw
Electric circular saw.
I cut with an electric circular saw.
I tried cutting with an electric circular saw.
Wow! If you have acrophobia...
I'm sorry.
Ew!
How did it feel?How did it feel to cut it?
I don't know. It felt like I could do it if I was really gentle.
It was so quick and easy.
I thought that even a beginner girl could do it.
I thought even a beginner girl could do it.
Once you get used to it, it's a piece of cake...
Tea ceremony?
Ha-ha-ha!
It's something like...
Here...
Three.
Hook it here.
Hold it down.
Four hundred...
Over here.
Like this.
Oh.
Move it.
Hold the line where your hand hits it.
Hold it tight.
Oh!
The second one's done!
I got it, I got it.
Here we go.
The line was a little off.
What about this one?
It's okay.
This is it, this is it, this is it.
Is it okay?
Huh.
A little something else.
I'm out.
I was able to cut it anyway.
Thank you for watching.
Oh, it looks fine! I got it!
The leg is cut!
Next, we will put more wood on top of the foot, so let's cut that wood.
This time, the length will change, so 545.
545.
545 to have it cut.
Wow!
A little bigger than the foot.
Here.
Here. Okay, okay.
There we go.
Oh!
Looks like this one's gonna be dry.
Five forty-five.
Here.
Ho!
Oh, not even close.
Ha-ha-ha. Dangerous.
Here.
Oh!
Oh, it's off!
Here we go.
It won't go back in.
Thank you for seeing me to the end.
Thank you very much for watching the show to the end.
Gentlemen, your channel has been previewed.
Please watch to the end.
A little something extra.
The sound of a dog.
Yeah, woof woof woof.
LOL
A happy dog.
Let's cut the part on the table.
Yes, sir.
I just had you cut four of them.
Cut the same length.
Open the cut.
Open the cut
Please do this for me.
Pull it in front of you.
This one moves.
Does it move?
It moves.
That's great.
Push it with this.
And then it goes again.
Just a little bit.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's working.
Move.
Move. Move.
move
It's moving.
I'm a little bit nervous now.
I'd like to cut it in stages.I'd like to cut the steps too.
It's fun.
I don't know if it's getting any better.
I don't know about that.
I'd like to cut it more and more.
Thank you very much.
I'm done cutting!
Mr. Kobayashi, we have finished cutting the materials.
Yes, we've finished cutting everything we need.
How was it?
It was my first time to really touch a saw.
I was a little nervous.
And then it just snapped.
What is this?
I've never done that before!
It's a lot of fun.
Is the leg finished now?
It's good that it's cut.
But there's also a fat one.
This is the one I made.
I was wondering if you could make this one too, Mr. Kobayashi.
It's got a little more dimples.
Like this.
When you put them together...
These will be the legs.
I've seen this before.
I'll have it carved here.
Looks difficult.
Here, at an angle.
If we don't do this, the circular saw will cut too deep.
I'll adjust the circular saw.
Adjust the circular saw.
please.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
I'm getting nervous.
Ha-ha-ha.
All right.
If you'll excuse me.
I want to take this one here, so I'm going to have this one cut too.
I want to fit this in here, so I'm going to cut a lot of lines here, and only then I'm going to take it out cleanly.
Oh!
Okay, here we go.
Oh, the first one.
Shift it a little bit at a time.
I want you to use the ammers and have your left hand hold it down and tap it.
Ooh!
Looks like a four season flake.
LOL!
Yes, it does.
If I can get it off that well.
That's great.
We'll have to clean it up, won't we?
Yes.
It's like you're taking it off with a thump, thump, thump, thump, like this.
Oh!
Ooh!
Five minutes have passed, and now it's time for the third time, so give me a break!
Oh!
It's rattling.
Clean all this up.
So this is how you do it.
This is how clean it's gonna be.
The sun is setting.
It's getting dark.
I wonder if I can make it home in time.
It'll be dark if I do it myself.
Okay, I'll take care of the rest.
Or rather, I'll ask Mr. Kobayashi to help me.
Pompompompompompompompompompompompompompompompompompompompompompompompomp!
Here's what it looks like.
Wow, it's done with the amount! That's great!
Lastly, let's cut it diagonally.
45 degrees.
Yes, I'll cut it.
Yes, sir.
And here, it says the degree.
Move it.
Oh.
45 degrees.
I wonder if the angle works too.
That's amazing.
Wow!
Oh, wow!
Is it backwards?
It's the other way around!
It's done!
That's great!
One pair done, three more to go!
Two more to go.
Oh, one more pair.
One more pair
I would like to make it!
Log Log DIY!
Next, we will assemble them!
Yes!
Using this impact driver
Oh!
Use the screws.
Impact driverImpact Driver
It's like stopping.
Yes!
The foundation.
Shall we assemble it?
Yes!
Like holding a pistol.
Turn it again with your index finger.
Hold the one you want to stop firmly.
A little at a time.
Oh, my God!
It's heavy! Human.
But it's heavy, but not that heavy?
Which one is it?
Stick it in a little bit.
Yes! Yes!
Yes. Oh, my gosh.
Turn it off just a little bit.
Oh, there's a lot of space.
It's okay, it's okay. It's closed.
Till there's no more gaps.
Oh, until there's no more?
Oh!
I'm forgetting the ball.
It's about to go up.
Wow!
That's the diagonal and the one you dug for me, isn't it?
Yes, that's right.
I'm going to attach them now.
We're going to attach them.
We're going to use these screws here to hold it in place.
A little bit more.
That's great.
This is the foot.
Feet.
Yes, sir.
A little more.
There you go.
It's done.
Mmm-hmm.
I'm going to attach the legs to the base
I'm going to put the feet on the base I just made.
Oh.
Yes, it's okay.
Okay. Okay.
Okay, okay.
Oh.
Yes, yes, yes. Oh, wow.
Poof! It's up.
It's almost a table.
We're gonna put this last slice on top.
And it sticks together like this.
Okay.
I'll drill a hole in the most important one.
I'll drill a hole.
Okay.
Stop the hole first so it doesn't move.
Oh...
It's hard.
It doesn't go in at all.
Try pushing harder and harder
Armor
Yes, sir.
Wow.
Pull it out.
While turning
While pushing
Up.
Yes, sir.
Oh, my God!
I got it, now!
If I hadn't pulled it out, I wouldn't have!
Huh.
Fast forward.
Yes, sir.
fast forward
Oh, they were so fast.
What's wrong?
Straight here.
Yes, sir.
It's tighter that way. - True.
That's true.
Well, you're good.
Oh, sorry.
You're good. Wow, I'm getting used to it.
Here you go.
It's done.
Oh! Finished!
Of course, Mr. Kobashi did a lot of work, but
I didn't think I could make a table like this.
I'm so happy!
Would you like to write something?
Yes! I will write something.
Excuse me.
Lindege Blue
Oh, no.
Here.
Take it.Get it.
It says, "Take it." Okay.
Okay, it's done.
I painted it in an artist's style, which I got a taste for when I painted the helmet.
How did you like it?
I don't think I'll be able to make it the first time. It's a bit like three-minute cooking.
I thought I'd end up using something that was already made.
But now that I've made it from home, I'm inspired to try different things.
If you liked it so far, please subscribe to my channel and give me a high rating!
See you next time! Bye bye!
Here is the product I used this time Plantex Glove Urethane Backless
The world's first Eco Mark certified product in the field of work gloves using plant-derived synthetic fibers.
The use of long fibers prevents dust from being generated.
The back of the hand is back-threaded for excellent ventilation.